A Guide to the Nelson C. Davis Papers FA048
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Personal Papers, 1913-1933; 1
  - Personal Papers - Articles, 1921-1933; 1.4
    - Articles - Reprints, May 1928-March 1930 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      Davis, N.C. and Shannon, R.C. Studies on yellow fever in South America. IV. Transmission experiments with 'Aedes aegypti'. The Journal of Experimental Medicine, 50:793-801, No. 6, December 1, 1929.
      Davis, N.C. and Shannon, R.C. Studies on yellow fever in South America. V. Transmission experiments with certain species of Culex and Aedes. The Journal of Experimental Medicine, 50:803-808, No. 6, December 1, 1929.
      Shannon, R.C., Burke, A.W. and Davis, N.C. Observations on released 'Stegomyia aegypti' (L.) with special reference to dispersion. The American Journal of Tropical Medicine, 10:145-150, No. 2, March 1930. 2 copies.
      Shannon, R.C. and Davis, N.C. The flight of 'Stegomyia aegypti (L)'. The American Journal of Tropical Medicine, 10:151-156, No. 2, March 1930. 2 copies.
    - Articles - Reprints, March 1930-March 1931 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      Davis, N.C. and Shannon, R.C. The location of yellow fever virus in infected mosquitoes and the possibility of hereditary transmission. The American Journal of Hygiene, 11:335-344, No. 2, March 1930.
      Davis, N.C. Susceptibility of capuchin (Cebus) monkeys to yellow fever virus. The American Journal of Hygiene, 11:321-334, No. 2, March 1930.
      Davis, N.C. The transmission of yellow fever. Experiments with the "woolly monkey" ('Lagothrix lagotricha Humbolt'), the "spider monkey" ('Ateleus ater F. Cuvier'), and the "squirrel monkey" ('Saimiri scireus Linnaeus'). The Journal of Experimental Medicine, 51:703-720, No. 5, May 1, 1930.
      Davis, N.C. The susceptibility of marmosets to yellow fever virus. The Journal of Experimental Medicine, 52:405-415, No. 3, September 1, 1930.
      Burke, A.W. and Davis, N.C. Notes on laboratory infections with yellow fever. The American Journal of Tropical Medicine, 10:419-426, No. 6, November 1930. 2 copies.
      Davis, N.C. The transmission of yellow fever. On the possibility of immunity in stegomyia mosquitoes. The American Journal of Tropical Medicine, 11:31-42, No. 1, January, 1931. 2 copies.
      Davis, N.C. A new anopheline mosquito from Para, Brazil. The American Journal of Hygiene, 13:345-348, No. 1, January 1931.
      Davis, N.C. Estudoes sobre febre amarella. O effeito do calor e do frio sobre o desenvolvimento da infectividade nos Aedes aegypti. Brasil-Medico, 45:77, No. 4, January 24, 1931.
      Davis, N.C. and Shannon, R.C. Studies on yellow fever in South America. Attempts to transmit the virus with certain aedine and sabethine mosquitoes and with triatomas (hemiptera). The American Journal of Tropical Medicine, 11:21-29, No. 1, January 1931.
      Davis, N.C. A note on the malaria-carrying Anophelines in Belem, Para, and in Natal, Rio Grande de Norte, Brazil. Rivista di Malariologia, 10:43-51, January-February, 1931. 2 copies.
      Davis, N.C. The transmission of yellow fever. Further experiments with monkeys of the New World. The American Journal of Tropical Medicine, 11:113-125, No. 2, March 1931.
      Davis, N.C. Use experimental de uma vacina clorofomada contra a febre amarella. (Experimental Use of a Chloroform-Treated Yellow Fever Vaccine). Brasil-Medico, 45:268, No. 12, March 21, 1931. 2 copies.
    - Articles - Reprints, July 1931-September 1932 (Box 8, Folder 55)
      Frobisher, M. Jr., Davis, N.C. and Shannon, R.C. On the failure of yellow fever virus to persist in a colony of 'Aedes aegypti'. The American Journal of Hygiene, 14:142-146, No. 1, July 1931. 2 copies.
      Davis, N.C. and Shannon, R.C. Further attempts to transmit yellow fever with mosquitoes of South America. The American Journal of Hygiene, 14:715-722, No. 3, November 1931. 2 copies.
      Davis, N. C. and Kumm, H.H.W. Further incrimination of 'Anophelos darlingi' Root as a transmitter of malaria. The American Journal of Tropical Medicine, 12:93-95, No. 1, January 1932.
      Davis, N.C. The effect of various temperatures in modifying the extrinsic incubation period of the yellow fever virus in 'Aedes aegypti'. The American Journal of Hygiene, 16:163-176, No. 1, July 1932.
      Soper, Fred L., Frobisher, M. Jr., Kerr, J.A. and Davis, N.C. Studies of the distribution of immunity to yellow fever in Brazil. I. Postepidemic survey of Mage, Rio de Janeiro, by complement-fixation and monkey-protection tests. The Journal of Preventive Medicine, 6:341-377, No. 5, September 1932. 2 copies.
    - Articles - Reprints, December 1932-August 1933 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      Davis, N.C., Lloyd, W. and Frobisher, M. Jr. The transmission of neurotropic yellow fever virus by Stegomyia mosquitoes. The Journal of Experimental Medicine, 56:853-865, No. 6, December 1, 1932. 2 copies.
      Davis, N.C. Attempts to transmit yellow fever virus with 'Triatoma megista' (Burmeister). The Journal of Parasitology, 19:209-214, No. 3, March 1933. 2 copies.
      Davis, N.C. and Serafim, Jose, Jr. Distribution of 'Aedes (Taeniorhynchus) taeniorhynchus' (Wiedemann) 'Aedes (Taeniorhynchus)' Jacobinae, new species. Annals of the Entomological Society of America, 26:13-19, March 1933. 2 copies.
      Davis, N.C. Notes on some South American mosquitoes. Annals of the Entomological Society of America, 26:277-295, No. 2, June 1933. 2 copies.
      Davis, N.C., Frobisher, M. Jr., and Lloyd, W. The titration of yellow fever virus in Stegomyia mosquitoes. The Journal of Experimental Medicine, 58:211-226, No. 2, August 1, 1933. 2 copies.
  - Personal Papers - Plates and Drawings, 1.5
    This subseries consists of a single undated folder of engraved plates and drawings of biological subjects made by Dr. Davis.
    - Plates and Drawings (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Professional Papers, 1921-1933; 2
  Series 2 is divided into 7 subseries:
  Subseries 1 - Porto Alegre, Brazil Subseries 2 - Field Notebooks Subseries 3 - Bahia, Brazil Subseries 4 - Reports Subseries 5 - Articles Subseries 6 - Monthly Bulletins Subseries 7 - File Card Bibliography
  The material in this series consists of documents related to service assignments undertaken by Dr. Davis with The Rockefeller Foundation. It includes monthly reports, some correspondence, maps of areas visited, examination charts, diaries, field note books, and an expense book.
  Dr. Davis's foreign service falls into two main divisions - the first (1922-1927) spent mainly in Brazil, where he engaged in hookworm and malaria control work; the second (1928-1933) as director of the Yellow Fever Laboratory in Bahia, Brazil. With the exception of some time spent in Argentina (July-December 1925 and January-July 1927), his activities are amply documented by the material in this series. Further correspondence is available in the Rockefeller Foundation Archives, Record Group 1.1, Series 305.I and 305.O.
  The laboratory diaries for the Yellow Fever Laboratory at Bahia originally consisted of seven bound and numbered handwritten volumes; of these, volume IV (February-October 1931) is missing. This volume was kept by Dr. Martin Frobisher, Jr., in the absence of Dr. Davis. A complete typescript of these diaries, including the missing volume, together with typescripts of some of Dr. Davis's field note books, may be found in the Rockefeller Foundation Archives, Record Group 1.1, Series 305.O.
  This series continues with typescript reports or articles sent to Dr. Davis for comment or information by officers of The Rockefeller Foundation, and concludes with copies of The International Health Board's newspaper in Brazil ("O Telescopio" - later, "O Saneamento").
  - Professional Papers - Porto Alegre, Brazil, 1921-1927; 2.1
    This subseries consists of reports, charts, graphs, examination records, an expense book, and field note books kept during Dr. Davis's first period of service in South America, spent primarily in Porto Alegre and Rio de Janeiro, Brazil.
    - Porto Alegre - Reports, 1921-1923 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Porto Alegre - Reports, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Porto Alegre - Reports, 1923, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Porto Alegre, 1924-1927 (Box 9, Folder 61)
      Maps and Charts, Experiment Records
    - Porto Alegre - Examination Records, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Porto Alegre - Expense Book, with Attachments, 1922-1927 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - 8 Graphs, Handdrawn, Showing Levels of Hookworm Infection, 1923; Large-format material. (Box 33, Folder 303)
    - 3 Printed Charts, Showing Use of Rockefeller Foundation Services in Brazil, 1923; Large-format material. (Box 33, Folder 304)
    - 6 Maps of Brazil or Portions of Brazil, circa 1923; Large-format material. (Box 33, Folder 305)
  - Professional Papers - Field Notebooks, 1922-1933; 2.2
    This subseries consists of laboratory notes, field observations, and miscellany.
    - Field Note Books, 1922-1926 (Box 9, Folder 64)
      1. January 12-April 21, 1922 2. July 7-October 31, 1923 3. January 14-27, 1925 4. March 3-April 5, 1926, with attachments.
    - Notebooks, 1922-1932 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      Field Note Books
      5. January-April 1930 6. May 23, 1930-January 8, 1931 7. January 22-March 16, 1931 8. December 6-15, 1932
      Miscellaneous Notebooks
      1. Portuguese-English Glossary, circa 1922 2. Bibliography, circa 1928.
    - Miscellaneous Notebooks, 1925-1933, undated (Box 10, Folder 66)
      3. Lab Record of Dr. A. da Silva Basilio, circa 1925 4. Employee Work Record, January-June 1933 5. Examination Record, undated.
  - Professional Papers - Bahia, Brazil, 1928-1933; 2.3
    This subseries contains lab diaries of the Yellow Fever Laboratory directed by Dr. Davis, consisting of six (originally seven) bound manuscript volumes.
    - Lab Diary I, July 7, 1928-August 31, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Lab Diary II, September 1, 1929-August 31, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Lab Diary III, September 1, 1930-February 18, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Lab Diary V, October 10, 1931-August 31, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Lab Diary VI, September 1, 1932-August 31, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Lab Diary VII, September 1-October 19, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Professional Papers - Reports, 1923-1930; 2.4
    This subseries contains reports sent to Dr. Davis by officers of The Rockefeller Foundation.
    - Reports (Box 11, Folder 73)
      1. "Experiments in Recovering Nematodes from the Soil" (c1923) 2. Report in Portuguese (September 16, 1923) 3. Report in Portuguese (September 21, 1923) 4. "Notes on Yellow Fever Work" (c1923) 5. S. T. Darling - "Summary Report for 1924: Field Studies in Malarial Control" 6. A. Missiroli - "Malaria Experiment Station: First Report 1925-26" 7. E.R. Rickard - "Quarterly Narrative Report of the Argentine Malaria Service, January-March 1930" 8. George K. Strode - "Report on Public Health Nursing in Denmark, May 1930."
    - Reports - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Professional Papers - Articles, c1923-c1932; 2.5
    This subseries consists of articles sent to Dr. Davis by officers of The Rockefeller Foundation.
    - Articles - Mark F. Boyd, "Introduction to Malariology", undated (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Articles (Box 12, Folder 76)
      Mark F. Boyd, "Introduction to Malariology", undated; Mark F. Boyd, et al., "Studies of the Epidemiology of Malaria in the Coastal Regions of Brazil", circa 1924.
    - Articles - Mark F. Boyd, et al, "Studies of the Epidemiology of Malaria in the Coastal Regions of Brazil", circa1924 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - Articles (Box 12, Folder 78)
      Henry R. Carter, "Epidemiology of Yellow Fever," circa 1929. George H. Ramsey, "Feveral Jaundice in the Province of Santa Maria, Colombia: Preliminary Report," circa 1932.
    - Articles (Box 12, Folder 79)
      George H. Ramsey, "Feveral Jaundice in the Province of Santa Maria, Colombia: Preliminary Report - Appendix," circa 1932. Miscellany
    - Articles - Miscellany (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Professional Papers - Monthly Bulletins, 1922-1933; 2.6
    This subseries includes the monthly bulletins of the International Health Board (later Division) in Brazil.
    - Monthly Bulletins (Box 12, Folder 81)
      "O Telescopio", August 1922-September 1922. "O Saneamento", October 1922-December 1923.
    - "O Saneamento", January 1924-April 1925 (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - "O Saneamento", May 1925-December 1933 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Professional Papers - File Card Bibliography, 2.7
    This subseries consists of bibliographical references to works on tropical diseases.
    - File Card Bibliography, undated (Box 13, Folder 84)
- Printed Matter, 1895-1935; 3
  Series 3 is divided into 4 subseries:
  Subseries 1 - Reprints by Rockefeller Foundation Personnel Subseries 2 - Reprints by Non-Rockefeller Foundation Individuals Subseries 3 - Monographs Subseries 4 - Periodicals
  The material in this series consists of reprints, monographs, and periodicals--mostly on medical topics related to Dr. Davis's work in hookworm, malaria, and yellow fever. It was gathered primarily as background material for his own research.
  - Printed Matter - Reprints by Rockefeller Foundation Personnel, 3.1
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by author.
    - Reprints (Box 14, Folder 85)
      Flexner, Simon - 2 reprints Hackett, Lewis W. - 4 reprints Heiser, Victor - 2 reprints Kumm, Henry W. - 4 reprints Lewis, Paul A. - 1 reprint Rickard, E.R. - 5 reprints Russell, F. F. - 1 reprint
    - Sawyer, W. A. (Box 14, Folder 86)
    - Shannon, Raymond C. (Box 14, Folder 87)
    - Soper, Fred L. (Box 14, Folder 88)
    - Reprints (Box 14, Folder 89)
      Soper, Fred L. - 7 reprints Anonymous - "Malaria: Motion Picture Film", 1923
  - Printed Matter - Reprints by Non-Rockefeller Foundation Individuals, 3.2
    - Abderhalden - Aragao (Box 14, Folder 90)
      Abderhalden, Emil - 1 reprint Almeido, A. Egydia - 1 reprint Andrade, Abelardo Marinho de - 1 reprint Andrade, Lessa de - 1 reprint Aragao, Henrique de Beurepaire - 3 reprints
    - Aragao - Araujo (Box 15, Folder 91)
      Aragao, Henrique de Beurepaire - 12 reprints Arana, Manuel Cervantes - 1 reprint Araujo, Eduardo de - 8 reprints
    - Arribalzaga - Baisas (Box 15, Folder 92)
      Arribalzaga, Felix Linch - 1 reprint Ashford, Bailey K. - 6 reprints Assumpacao, Lucas de - 1 reprint Auchincloss, Hugh - 1 reprint Autran, Eugenio - 1 reprint Axtmeyer, Joseph H. - 1 reprint Baisas, F.E. - 2 reprints
    - Barnes - Benarroch (Box 15, Folder 93)
      Barnes, M.E. - 1 reprint Barker, Marshall A. - 2 reprints Barrand, P.J. - 2 reprints Bates, J.E. - 1 reprint Bauer, Johannes H. - 1 reprint Bedford, G.A.H. - 1 reprint Benarroch, Elias - 1 reprint
    - Bird - Burke (Box 15, Folder 94)
      Bird, W. - 2 reprints Blanc, George - 2 reprints Brethes, Juan - 4 reprints Britto, Oscar de - 1 reprint Burke, Alice M.B. - 1 reprint
    - Buxton - Chandler (Box 15, Folder 95)
      Buxton, Patrick A. - 1 reprint Carrion, A.L. - 4 reprints Carter, Henry F. - 1 reprint Carter, Henry R. - 2 reprints Chandler, Asa C. - 3 reprints
    - Chandler, Asa C. (Box 15, Folder 96)
    - Chandler - Christopher (Box 16, Folder 97)
      Chandler, Asa C. - 5 reprints Christopher, S.R. - 2 reprints
    - Christopher - Consoli (Box 16, Folder 98)
      Christopher, S.R. - 4 reprints Ciferri, Rafaelle - 3 reprints Consoli, Nicolo - 1 reprint
    - Cook - Covell (Box 16, Folder 99)
      Cook, D.H. - 3 reprints Cossio, Rufino - 1 reprint Covell, G. - 4 reprints
    - Covell - Darling (Box 16, Folder 100)
      Covell, G. - 3 reprints Covell, W.P. - 1 reprint Craighie, James - 1 reprint Cunha, A. Marques da - 2 reprints Dalman, Luiz Maria - 1 reprint Danks, W.B.C. - 1 reprint Darling, S.T. - 1 reprint
    - Del Negro - Ferguson (Box 16, Folder 101)
      Del Negro, Carlos - 1 reprint Dinger, J.E. - 2 reprints Docherty, J.F. - 1 reprint Dunn, Lawrence H. - 1 reprint Dyar, Harrison G. - 1 reprint Earle, Walter C. - 2 reprints Ferguson, E.W. - 1 reprint
    - Ferreira - Gilbert (Box 16, Folder 102)
      Ferreira, Sinbe - 1 reprint Ferrell, John A. - 1 reprint Fialho, Amadeu - 2 reprints Findlay, G.M. - 1 reprint Fox, Herbert - 1 reprint Fassig, Oliver L. - 2 reprints Fraga, Clementin - 4 reprints Frobisher, Martin Jr. - 1 reprint Gilbert, Isabelle - 1 reprint
    - Gonzalez - Haagen (Box 17, Folder 103)
      Gonzalez, Eudora - 1 reprint Gordon, R. Montgomery - 7 reprints Gorgas, W.C. - 1 reprint Grant, John B. - 2 reprints Haagen, E. - 2 reprints
    - Hazemann - Hirst (Box 17, Folder 104)
      Hazemann, R.H. - 1 reprint Hernandez, Luis F. - 2 reprints Hill, Rolla B. - 1 reprint Hindle, Edwards - 7 reprints Hinman, E. Harold - 2 reprints Hirst, L. Fabian - 1 reprint
    - Hodson, W.E.H. (Box 17, Folder 105)
    - Hoffmann, C. - Hoffmann, W. (Box 17, Folder 106)
      Hoffmann, Carlos C. - 7 reprints Hoffmann, J.M. - 3 reprints Hoffmann, W.H. - 14 reprints
    - Holt - Kendrick (Box 17, Folder 107)
      Holt, Rufus L. - 2 reprints Hudson, N. Paul - 1 reprint Isern, A. Fernos - 1 reprint Ishikara, S. - 1 reprint Jacob, A. - 1 reprint JAmes, S.D. - 2 reprints Kehar, N.D. - 1 reprint Kendrick, J.F. - 1 reprint
    - Kerr - Lambert (Box 17, Folder 108)
      Kerr, J. Austin - 2 reprints Kesten, Beatrice M. - 2 reprints King, W.V. - 1 reprint Klinger, I.J. - 1 reprint Knott, James - 1 reprint Koppick, Enrique - 1 reprint Kuczynski, Max H. - 2 reprints Kuroya, Masahito - 1 reprint Lahille, F. - 1 reprint Lambert, Robert A. - 3 reprints
    - Lambert - Lima (Box 18, Folder 109)
      Lambert, S. M. - 4 reprints Lane, Jone - 2 reprints Leach, Charles N. - 1 reprint Lessa, Gustavo - 1 reprint Lima, A. da Costa - 9 reprints
    - Lima - Low (Box 18, Folder 110)
      Lima, H. da Rocha - 7 reprints Lloyd, Wray - 1 reprint Low, G. Carmichael - 1 reprint
    - Lutz, Adolpho (Box 18, Folder 111)
    - Lutz - McKinley (Box 18, Folder 112)
      Lutz, Adolpho - 3 reprints Macdonald, G. - 1 reprint Mackerras, I.M. - 2 reprints McKenley, Earl B. - 6 reprints
    - Maciel - Marrin (Box 18, Folder 113)
      Maciel, Heraldo - 2 reprints Mandry, Oscar Costa - 2 reprints Marchoux, E. - 4 reprints Marrin, Rafael E. - 1 reprint
    - Marques - Mazza (Box 18, Folder 114)
      Marques, Eduardo - 1 reprint Marques, Luis A. de Azeuedo - 1 reprint Mayne, Bruce - 6 reprints Mazza, Salvador - 4 reprints
    - Mazza - Meuse (Box 19, Folder 115)
      Mazza, Salvador - 8 reprints Meillon, Bathade - 1 reprint Meuse, Carl - 1 reprint
    - Miyagawa - Mulligan (Box 19, Folder 116)
      Miyagawa, Yonegi - 1 reprint Monteiro, J. Jemos - 4 reprints Morales-Loera, Pablo - 1 reprint Muehlens, P. - 1 reprint Mulligan, H.W. - 1 reprint
    - Nagaya - Nuttall (Box 19, Folder 117)
      Nagaya, Takeguma - 4 reprints Nakajima, Katsumi - 2 reprints Neiva, A. - 1 reprint Nono, Andrews M. - 1 reprint Nuttall, George H.F. - 6 reprints
    - O'Connor - Ozawa (Box 19, Folder 118)
      O'Connor, F.W. - 3 reprints Okada, Ryoichi - 4 reprints Oliveira, Rennifio de - 1 reprint Ortiz, Pedro N. - 1 reprint Otero, Pablo Morales - 1 reprint Ozawa, Makoto - 1 reprint
    - Parreiras - Philip (Box 19, Folder 119)
      Parreiras, Decia - 1 reprint Parsons, Allan C. - 1 reprint Paterson, Guillermo C. - 1 reprint Payne, George - 1 reprint Penido, J.C.N. - 1 reprint Peryassu, Antonio - 1 reprint Pessoa, Samuel Barnsley - 1 reprint Petrocchi, Juana - 1 reprint Pettit, Auguste - 6 reprints Philps, Earle B. - 1 reprint Philip, Cornelius B. - 1 reprint
    - Pinto - Rolim (Box 19, Folder 120)
      Pinto, Genserico de Souza - 3 reprints Pomales, Americo - 1 reprint Posse, Justino S. - 1 reprint Postmus, S. - 1 reprint Puri, I.M. - 2 reprints Rolim, Ernesto - 1 reprint
    - Russell, Paul F. (Box 20, Folder 121)
    - Russell, Paul F. (Box 20, Folder 122)
    - Sabate - Senior-White (Box 20, Folder 123)
      Sabate, Eduardo L. - 1 reprint Sakrui, Shintaro - 1 reprint Scharff, J.W. - 1 reprint Schuffner, W. - 1 reprint Sella, Massimo - 1 reprint Senevet, G. - 2 reprints Senior-White, Ronald - 5 reprints
    - Serra - Sinton (Box 20, Folder 124)
      Serra, Americo - 2 reprints Sherman, Henry C. - 2 reprints Shibata, Makoto - 1 reprint Shinmen, Masuru - 2 reprints Silva, Flaviano - 3 reprints Sinton, J.A. - 8 reprints
    - Sinton - Suarez (Box 20, Folder 125)
      Sinton, J.A. - 11 reprints Smillie, W.G. - 1 reprint Stefanopoulo, Georges J. - 5 reprints Strickland, C. - 3 reprints Stumberg, John E. - 1 reprint Suarez, Lenard - 1 reprint
    - Sweet - Symposium on Malaria (Box 20, Folder 126)
      Sweet, W.C. - 3 reprints Swellengregel, N.H. - 1 reprint Symposium on Malaria - 5 reprints
    - Tampi - Theiler (Box 21, Folder 127)
      Tampi, M.K. - 1 reprint Tauney, Affonso d'E. - 1 reprint Tayler, R.M. - 1 reprint Teixeira, J. Castro - 1 reprint Theiler, Max - 2 reprints
    - Torgerson - Torres (Box 21, Folder 128)
      Torgerson, William R. - 2 reprints Torres, C. Magarinos - 4 reprints Torres, Octavio - 2 reprints
    - Townshend - Walker (Box 21, Folder 129)
      Townshend, Charles H.T. - 1 reprint Travassos, Lauro - 1 reprint Vaughn, Emmett I. - 1 reprint Velder, E.B. - 2 reprints Vianna, Dr. Jr. - 1 reprint Wada, Kaoru - 1 reprint Wakeman, A.L. - 1 reprint Walker, Ernest Linwood - 4 reprints
    - Walker - Wenyon (Box 21, Folder 130)
      Walker, Ernest Linwood - 4 reprints Washburn, B.E. - 1 reprint Wassermann, Harry - 1 reprint Wenyon, C.M. - 2 reprints
    - West - Yamada (Box 21, Folder 131)
      West, Augustus P. - 1 reprint Williamson, K.B. - 3 reprints Yamada, Shinichiro - 4 reprints
    - Yeager - Zetch (Box 21, Folder 132)
      Yeager, Clark H. - 3 reprints Young, Shutso - 1 reprint Young, T.C. McCombie - 1 reprint Zetch, James - 1 reprint
  - Printed Matter - Monographs, 1901-1935; 3.3
    - "African Conference on Yellow Fever: Dakar, April 1928." Paris, 1929. (Box 22, Folder 133)
    - Araujo, Eduardo Ferreira de. "Do Mycetema Pedis no Brazil." Bahia, 1930. (Box 22, Folder 134)
    - Bahn, P.H. "Filariasis and Elephantiasis in Fiji." London, 1912. (Box 22, Folder 135)
    - Barbieri, Antonio and Penna, J. "El Paludisomo." 2nd. Edition. Buenos Aires, 1925. (Box 22, Folder 136)
    - Borel, B. "Les Moustiquoes de la Cochinchine et du Sud-Amman." Paris, 1930. (Box 22, Folder 137)
    - Boyaer, Rupert. "Yellow Fever Prophylaxis in New Orleans." London, 1906. (Box 22, Folder 138)
    - Boyd, Mark F. and Aris, F.W. "Malaria Survey: Jamaica." Kingston, 1926. (Box 22, Folder 139)
    - Brant, Mario. "O Alcoolismo." Bella Horizonte (Brazil), 1923. (Box 22, Folder 140)
    - Buchanan, G. "Spriochaetal Jaundice." London, 1927. (Box 22, Folder 141)
    - Bureau for Increasing the Use of Quinine. "Malaria and the Child." Amsterdam, 1932. (Box 22, Folder 142)
    - Campbell, Janet M. "Maternal Mortality." London, 1924. (Box 22, Folder 143)
    - Christopher, S.R. et al. "How to do a Malaria Survey." Calcutta, 1928. (Box 22, Folder 144)
    - Columbia, Republic of. "Reglamento del Departmento de Uncinariasis." Bogota, 1926. (Box 22, Folder 145)
    - "Control of Endemic Diseases in the Netherlands Indies." Weltevreden, 1929. (Box 22, Folder 146)
    - Cossio, Rufino. "La Campana Antipaludica en Tucuman." Tucuman (Argentina), 1928. (Box 22, Folder 147)
    - Deeks, W.E. and James, W.M. "A Report on Hemoglobinic Fever in the Canal Zone." Mount Hope (C.I.), 1911. (Box 22, Folder 148)
    - Departmento de Salubriada Publica. "La Historia de un Nino." Mexico, 1930. (Box 22, Folder 149)
    - Deparmento Nacional de Higiene. "La bucha antimalarica en la Argentine." Buenos Aires, 1928. (Box 22, Folder 150)
    - Destouches, Louis Henri. "A Quinina terapeuitica." Amsterdam, 1931. (Box 22, Folder 151)
    - Fontonelle, J.P. "Cuidado Prenataes." Rio de Janeiro, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 152)
    - Fraga, Clementin. "A febre Amarella no Brasil." Rio de Janiero, 1930. (Box 22, Folder 153)